Here we are at Michael Freeman, programmer of pizza party, and we're going to do an example.
这里是Michael Freeman，披萨派对程序的开发者，我们将做一个示例。
So pizza party is command line software to order pizza.
披萨派对是一个通过命令行订购披萨的软件。
Why don't we take a look at the help on?
我们为什么不看看帮助信息呢？
Okay, here we go.
好的，开始吧。
Here is the syntax of pizza party.
这里是披萨派对的语法。
Yep.
是的。
Program.
程序。
The options.
选项。
How many pizzas?
要多少个披萨？
What size and what kind of crust?
什么尺寸，什么类型的饼皮？
All right, so let's take a look at the flags.
好的，让我们看看这些标志。
Here is username password for your dominoes account.
这里是你的达美乐账户的用户名密码。
Input file, which allows you to order pizzas in batch if you're throwing a pizza party.
输入文件，如果你要举办披萨派对，可以让你批量订购披萨。
Vervose, quiet, and force, our typical command line arguments.
详细、安静和强制，这些都是典型的命令行参数。
All right, standard Unix stuff.
好的，标准的Unix内容。
Standard Unix stuff.
标准的Unix内容。
And here's some of the flags.
这里还有一些标志。
Onions, screen peppers, mushrooms, olives, tomatoes, pineapple.
洋葱、青椒、蘑菇、橄榄、番茄、菠萝。
Of course, if you haven't noticed yet, these are the toppings.
当然，如果你还没注意到，这些都是配料。
Cheddar cheese, pepperoni, sausage, ham, bacon, ground beef, grilled chicken, anchovies, and extra sauce.
切达奶酪、意大利辣肠、香肠、火腿、培根、牛肉末、烤鸡、凤尾鱼和额外的酱汁。
So why don't we order a pizza?
那我们为什么不订购一个披萨呢？
Here you go.
给你。
What do you want on it?
你想要什么配料？
Pepperoni?
意大利辣肠？
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
Mushrooms?
蘑菇？
Yep.
是的。
Anything else?
还要别的吗？
No, that's cool.
不，这样就好。
How many?
多少个？
Just one.
只要一个。
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
What size?
什么尺寸？
Medium.
中号。
And what kind of crust?
什么样的饼皮？
Hmm, thin.
嗯，薄饼皮。
Thin crust.
薄饼皮。
Okay, here we go.
好的，开始吧。
All right, so here's our confirmation.
好的，这是我们的确认信息。
1248 is your price.
1248是你的价格。
Are you ready?
准备好了吗？
Yeah.
是的。
There you go.
给你。
All right.
好的。
And then it bumps us back to the command line.
然后它把我们带回到命令行。
You know, ready for fun stuff.
你知道，准备好做有趣的事情了。
Yeah, so let's see what time it is.
是的，让我们看看现在几点。
All right, so 621.
好的，6点21分。
So we'll see if the pizza comes in a half hour.
所以我们看看披萨是否会在半小时内送达。
Oh, there we go.
哦，开始了。
See if the pizza comes in a half hour.
看看披萨是否会在半小时内送达。
All right.
好的。
I'm hungry.
我饿了。
All right.
好的。
Hello.
你好。
There we go.
我们开始吧。
What do you guys want?
你们想要什么？
It comes to 1248.
总共是1248。
Thank you.
谢谢。
How much more back to it, right?
还要加多少钱，对吧？
1248.
1248。
Five up.
五元以上。
Oh, thin crust.
哦，薄饼皮。
Oh, nice.
哦，不错。
I never had.
我从来没有吃过。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Yeah, right?
是啊，对吧？
It's good.
很好。
Yeah.
是的。